Contact

shellz1984heart@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/michelecoleman-the-rn-for-you (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Nursing Healthcare Operating Room

Languages

English (Native or Bilingual)

Michele Coleman

Operating Room Nurse at Maxium Health Care Svc Greater Chicago Area

Summary

Experienced Operating Room Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Gynecology, Nursing Documentation, Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS), Healthcare, and Basic Life Support (BLS). Strong healthcare services professional with a Associate of Science (A.S.) focused in Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse from ITT Technical Institute-Indianapolis.

Experience

Maxium Health Care Svc Operating Room Nurse January 2019 - Present (1 year 7 months) Greater Chicago Area

Accountable Healthcare Staffing Registered Nurse Perioperative Nurse October 2018 - January 2019 (4 months) Greater Chicago Area

Fastaff Travel Nursing
Registered Nurse Perioperative Nurse
February 2018 - October 2018 (9 months)
Brooklyn, New York

St. Joseph Medical Center
Operating Room Nurse
September 2015 - June 2018 (2 years 10 months)
Chicago, Illinois

University of Chicago Medicine Surgical Technician September 2013 - September 2015 (2 years 1 month) Greater Chicago Area As a Surgical Technologist I am involved in process improvement or quality initiatives related to, but outside of, Perioperative Services. I also assist the nursing and medical staff in providing care to patients undergoing surgical intervention and performance of surgical scrub technologist duties; collaborate with nursing and other disciplines, when necessary, to revise the plan of care to meet the changing needs of the patient. I have constant contact with the Operating Room staff, physicians, clerical staff, anesthesia staff and materials management.

Adventist Hinsdale Hospital
Surgical Technician
August 2012 - November 2014 (2 years 4 months)
Hinsdale, IL

I performed patient care tasks and patient care procedures necessary to provide for care, comfort and safety of patient. I also functioned as a scrub person during c/sections. Sets-up supplies and breaks down surgical rooms. I acted as a support for the RN with patient care and the Unit Secretary with desk duties under the direction of the RN. My day-to-day responsibilities equire good use of judgment regarding timely and appropriate communication with team members and hospital staff. Recognizes the need for teamwork and functions as part of a multi-disciplinary team.

Education

ITT Technical Institute-Indianapolis
Associate of Science (A.S.), Registered Nursing/Registered
Nurse · (2012 - 2015)

Brown Mackie College-Indianapolis
Associate of Science (A.S.), Surgical Technology/Technologist · (2010 - 2012)